Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2016.0035, 1938-2016 (bulk 2008-2016)
  - Eddie Loftus Photo CD: Men's Lacrosse (Box 302 (UA2016-0035.13))
  - Two Men's basketball media guides, 2014-2015 (Box 302 (UA2016-0035.13))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country Binder, 2010-2011 (Box 303 (UA2016-0035.14))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country Binder, 2011-2012 (Box 303 (UA2016-0035.14))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country Binder, 2012-2013 (Box 303 (UA2016-0035.14))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country Binder, 2008-2009 (Box 304 (UA2016-0035.15))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country Binder, 2009-2010 (Box 304 (UA2016-0035.15))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country Binder, 2011-2012 (Box 304 (UA2016-0035.15))
  - Field Hockey Binder, 2010 (Box 304 (UA2016-0035.15))
  - Football Media Guides, 2013 (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Football Clips, 2012 (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Bronko Nagurski Trophy Programs, 2015 (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various rowing photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various football photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various cheerleading photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various Men's basketball photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various volleyball photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various fencing photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various baseball photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various athletics staff photo disks (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - NCAA Outdoor Track and Field photo disk (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Women's tennis media guide, 2008-2009 (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Various years fencing results (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Rowing, 2011-2012 (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Rowing, 2014 (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Starting at the Finish Line DVD (Box 305 (UA2016-0035.16))
  - Duke Men's basketball game-by-game files, 2015-2016 (Box 306 (UA2016-0035.17))
  - Official Scorer's Book, 2015-2016 (Box 306 (UA2016-0035.17))
  - Various Periodicals (Box 307 (UA2016-0035.18))
  - unknown (Box 308 (UA2016-0035.19))
- UA2017.0067, 1927-2016 (bulk 2015-2017)
  - Media Guide: Women's Basketball, 2016-2017 (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Clippings: Women's Basketball, 2016-2017 (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Women's Basketball, 2015-2016 (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Oderah Chidom: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Kendall Cooper: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Crystal D. Primm: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Blue/White Scrimmage 10/30/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Charleston (WVa) (Exhibition) 11/6/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Liberty 11/11/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Penn 11/15/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Longwood (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Grand Canyon 11/17/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Vanderbilt 11/20/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Old Dominion 11/22/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Long Beach State 11/25/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Pepperdine 11/27/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Rutgers 12/1/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - South Carolina 12/4/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Elon 12/8/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Villanova 12/21/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Kentucky 12/29/16: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Louisville 1/2/17: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Georgia Tech 1/5/17: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - Florida State 1/8/17: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - North Carolina 1/12/17: Women's Basketball (Box 310 (UA2017-0067.1))
  - NC State 1/15/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Virginia Tech 1/19/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Boston College 1/22/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Notre Dame 1/26/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Wake Forest 1/29/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Clemson 2/2/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Virginia 2/5/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Syracuse 2/10/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Pittsburgh 2/12/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Wake Forest 2/16/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Miami 2/19/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - North Carolina 2/26/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Syracuse 3/3/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Miami 3/4/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Notre Dame 3/5/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Hampton 3/18/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Duke vs Hampton NCAA 1st Round: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Oregon 3/20/17: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Duke vs Oregon NCAA 2nd Round: Women's Basketball (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Media Guide: Women's Golf, 2016-2017 (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Hee Wook (Sandy) Choi (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Gurbani Singh (Box 311 (UA2017-0067.2))
  - Football Game-by-Game Folders (Games 1-12), 2015 (Box 312 (UA2017-0067.3))
  - Football Game-by-Game Folders (Game 13), 2015 (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Football Clippings, 2016 (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Joseph Ajeigbe: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Andrew Bailey: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Dan Beilinson: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Johndre Bennett: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Casey Blaser: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Zach Boden: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Breon Borders: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Brandon Boyce: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Jacob Brodner: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Phillip Carter: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - James Cockey: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Jela Duncan: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - DeVon Edwards: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Grant Hall: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Thomas Hennessy: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Allen Jackson: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Jake Kite: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Dillon Leovic: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - DeQuavais Mann: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Corbin McCarthy: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Anthony Nash: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Marquis Price: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Erich Schneider: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Deondre Singleton: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Thomas Sirk: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Alex Skidmore: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Ryan Smith: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Wyatt Smith: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Danny Stirt: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Tanner Stone: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Kyle Wellner: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - A.J. Wolf: Football (Box 313 (UA2017-0067.4))
  - Men's Tennis, 2016-2017 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Andrew DeJoy: Men's Tennis (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Vincent Lin: Men's Tennis (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - TJ Pura: Men's Tennis (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Field Hockey, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Robin Blazing: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Hunter Bracale: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Heather Morris: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Aisling Naughton: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Meghan Norair: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Chessie Ruffell: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Savannah Story: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Kelsey Wagner: Field Hockey (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Lee Christensen: Swimming and Diving (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Benedict Parfit: Swimming and Diving (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - James Peek: Swimming and Diving (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Adriaan Venter: Swimming and Diving (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Swimming and Diving, 2016-2017 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball, 2015 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Laura Williams: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Cindy Marina: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Sasha Karelov: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Maggie Deichmeister: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Chloe DiPasquale: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Emily Sklar: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Jamie Stivers: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Jordan Tucker: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Alyse Whitaker: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Breanna Atkinson: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Christina Vucich: Volleyball (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Baseball, 2016 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball, 2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - CD: Duke Sports Hall of Fame Portraits & Headshots (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - DVD: A Cut Above: 100 Seasons of Duke Basketball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - FB Coach David Cutcliffe Bobby Dodd Coach of the Year Coin (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Football from Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1937 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Football photos, 1930s (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Duke football vs. NC State game program, 1927 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Zeke Young: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Zack Kesterson: baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Luke Glavin: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - James Ziemba: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Jalen Phillips: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Cristian Perez: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Cameron Neal: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Kevin Lewallyn: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Nick Hendrix: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Evan Dougherty: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Thomas Crispi: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Bailey Clark: baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Karl Blum: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Justin Bellinger: Baseball (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Liza Bragg: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Brittany Friese: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Jaimee Gundry: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Brittany Kahn: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Kirby Quinn: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Maddie Rusch: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Lindsay Schlichte: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Ashleigh Shanley: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Jessie Sutherland: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Colleen Wixted: Women's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rahul Chokshi: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Bradley Cline: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Kevin Fraser: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Marco Hosfeld: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Peter Kropp: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Joey Maginnis: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Michael Miller: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Emir Ozsuer: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Dylan Payne: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Parker Pearson: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Michael Seaberg: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Eric Strickland: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Kaz Takabayashi: Men's Swimming and Diving (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Bobak Shadpoor: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Alex Merriman: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Christopher Monti: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Ethan Yu: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Julia Lee: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rita Somogyi: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Emmeline Yoo: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Alexandra Viqueria: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Wendi Oppenheim: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Tara Mullen-Boustiha: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Natalie Moszxzynski: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Samantha Meyers: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Libby Malcolm: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Cheng Ma: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Samantha Lee: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Angelica Hubbard: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Sarah Collins: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Isabella Barna: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Jacob Wiener: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Charles Copti: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Michael DeVito: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Eugene Chung: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Ted Cho: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Edward Chen: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Alexander Szilagyi: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rod Shayesteh: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Colin Colter: Fencing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rowing, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Tani O'Neill: Rowing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Elizabeth Horne: Rowing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Phoebe Donovan: Rowing (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Tennis, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Chalena Scholl: Tennis (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Alyssa Smith: Tennis (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Madeline Kopp: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Michael Wilson: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Stephen Shine: Track and Field/Cross Country (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Dylan Murphy: Track and Field/Cross Country (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Ashton Huey: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Chaz Hawkins: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Connor Hall: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Daniel Moore: Track and Field/Cross Country (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Michal Filipczak: Track and Field/Cross Country (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Madison Granger: Track and Field/Cross Country (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Robert Rohner: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Daniel Golubovic: Track and Field (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Lars Kiel: Women's Lacrosse (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
- UA2018.0052, 1959-circa 2017
  - Duke Women's Golf Association Club Tournaments scrapbook, 1959-1985 (Box 317 (UA2018-0052.1))
  - Dick Groat letter and photocopy (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Slides and photographs of men's basketball, Women's field hockey, men's lacrosse, and football (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Football photo posters (Oversize-folder 3)